A Guide to the Student Council Office Administrative Files, 1987-1991
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Student Council Office Administrative Files 1987-1991
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-23/2/4.971
This collection consists of 8,200 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred by Pat Payne, Student Council's Office, Newcomb Hall, University of Virginia on 1997 September 26.
Scope and Content Information
The papers consist of topical files of the president of the Student Council.
Contents List
- SERIES I: Topical Files
  - Academics Committee 1987-1991 (Box 1)
  - Activities Coordinating Committee 1987-1991 (Box 1)
  - Admissions Committee 1987-1991 (Box 1)
  - Advantage Advertising 1990 July 9 (Box 1)
  - Academic Advising 1987-1989 (Box 1)
  - Alcohol 1987-1991 (Box 1)
  - Alderman Library Air Quality 1989-1991 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Association 1987-1991 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Outstanding Teaching Award-Christopher Johns 1990 (Box 1)
  - American Association of University Student (AAUS) (2 Folders) 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - American Association of University Students (AAUS) 1990-1991 (Box 2)
  - Apartheid Simulation 1989-1991 (Box 2)
  - Appropriations Committee (2 Folders) 1987-1991 (Box 2)
  - Assemblage 1990 (Box 2)
  - Assessment (2 Folders) 1989-1991 (Box 2)
  - Athletics 1987-1989 (Box 2)
  - Basketball Seating 1988-1989 (Box 3)
  - Berkeley Exchange 1988-1991 (Box 3)
  - Black Concerns Committee 1987-1991 (Box 3)
  - Black Faculty 1987-1989 (Box 3)
  - Black Student Leaders 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - Blue Ridge Area Food Bank 1988-1990 (Box 3)
  - Board of Visitors (BOV) (2 Folders) 1987-1991 (Box 3)
  - Board of Visitors (BOV)-Minutes (3 Folders) 1987-1991 (Box 4)
  - Board of Visitors (BOV)-Correspondence 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Book Exchange 1987-1989 (Box 4)
  - Budget Committee 1987-1992 (Box 4)
  - Budget and Finance-Tuition and Fees 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - By-Laws 1987-1991 (Box 5)
  - Calendar 1987-1991 (Box 5)
  - Chinese Students 1989-1991 (Box 5)
  - City Council 1988-1990 (Box 5)
  - Class Registration 1988-1989 (Box 5)
  - Commission on the 21st Century 1989-1991 (Box 5)
  - Committee Handbook 1987-1988 (Box 5)
  - Committee Overview 1988-1991 (Box 5)
  - Common Reading Experience 1989-1991 (Box 5)
  - Community Concerns Committee 1987-1991 (Box 5)
  - Conferences 1989-1991 (Box 5)
  - Constitution 1988-1991 (Box 5)
  - Contracted Independent Organizations (CIO) 1988-1989 (Box 6)
  - Contracted Independent Organizations (CIO)-Proposals 1987-1988 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence (3 Folders) 1987-1991 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence (3 Folders) 1987-1991 (Box 7)
  - Course Evaluation Book 1987-1991 (Box 7)
  - Development 1988-1989 (Box 7)
  - Dining Services 1988-1989 (Box 7)
  - Divestment 1987-1991 (Box 7)
  - Directory of International Students, Faculty and Scholars 1984-1987 (Box 8)
  - Drug Free Schools and Campuses Task Force 1988-1990 (Box 8)
  - Economic Analysis 1989-1991 (Box 8)
  - Education Update 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Election Committee 1987-1991 (Box 8)
  - Election Rules Committee 1987-1991 (Box 8)
  - Enrollment Expansion 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Environment/Recycling 1989-1991 (Box 8)
  - Ern Award 1987-1990 (Box 8)
  - Escort Service 1987-1991 (Box 8)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences 1988-1990 (Box 8)
  - Faculty Handbook 1987-1989 (Box 8)
  - Faculty Relations Committee 1987-1988 (Box 8)
  - Financial Aid Committee Minutes 1990-1991 (Box 9)
  - First Year Council 1987-1989 (Box 9)
  - Floyd Group 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Food and Transportation Committee 1987-1989 (Box 9)
  - First Year Seminar 1988-1989 (Box 9)
  - Fourth Year Class 1987-1989 (Box 9)
  - Freedom of Information Act Virginia Code 2.1-343, 344, 345 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Gay/Lesbian Concerns 1987-1991 (Box 9)
  - Goals 1989-1991 (Box 9)
  - Graduation 1987-1989 (Box 9)
  - Handicap Concerns 1987-1989 (Box 9)
  - Health Insurance Proposals 1987-1990 (Box 9)
  - Hookbook 1987-1991 (Box 9)
  - Housing and Safety (2 Folders) 1987-1991 (Box 10)
  - Interested Students 1987-1988 (Box 10)
  - Lawn Selections 1987-1989 (Box 10)
  - Lawn Use Policy 1987-1988 (Box 10)
  - Lease Agreement: Peabody/Newcomb Hall 1990-1991 (Box 10)
  - Legislation 1987-1991 (Box 10)
  - Madison Award 1987-1988 (Box 10)
  - Married Concerns 1987-1988 (Box 10)
  - Master Plan 1989-1991 (Box 10)
  - Mid-Year Report 1988-1989 (Box 10)
  - Minority Concerns 1987-1991 (Box 10)
  - Minority Fellowship Program 1987-1988 (Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous (5 Folders) 1988-1991 (Box 11)
  - Morn Plaza Dedication 1989-1991 (Box 11)
  - Newcomb Hall Crawl 1990 (Box 11)
  - News Articles 1987-1991 (Box 12)
  - Non-discrimination Clause 1987-1988 (Box 12)
  - Office Organization 1989-1991 (Box 12)
  - Orientation 1987-1989 (Box 12)
  - Orientation Week 1987-1991 (Box 12)
  - Outreach Program 1987-1988 (Box 12)
  - Personal Meetings 1990 July (Box 12)
  - Physical Plant 1988-1991 (Box 12)
  - Potential People 1989-1991 (Box 12)
  - Presidential Advisory Committee (PAC) 1987-1989 (Box 12)
  - Presidential Nominations 1988-1990 (Box 12)
  - President Search 1988-1990 (Box 12)
  - President's Retreat 1987-1990 (Box 12)
  - Projects 1988-1990 (Box 12)
  - Publicity Committee 1987-1989 (Box 13)
  - Race Relations 1987-1991 (Box 13)
  - Racial Harassment-Teleconference 1988-1990 (Box 13)
  - Retreat (2 Folders) 1987-1990 (Box 13)
  - Round Table 1987-1988 (Box 13)
  - Scholarship Committee 1987-1989 (Box 13)
  - Second Year Council 1991 (Box 13)
  - Security Committee 1987-1989 (Box 13)
  - Self-Scheduled Exams 1988-1989 (Box 13)
  - Semester Reports 1987-1989 (Box 13)
  - Sexism Workshop 1990 (Box 14)
  - Sexual Assault 1987-1990 (Box 14)
  - Sharing Charlottesville 1987-1988 (Box 14)
  - Speakers-Council 1987-1989 (Box 14)
  - State Council for Higher Education of Virginia (SCHEV) 1988-1991 (Box 14)
  - Strategic Management Techniques 1988-1990 (Box 14)
  - Student Activities Committee 1987-1990 (Box 14)
  - Student Association of Virginia 1988-1990 (Box 14)
  - Student Complaints (Restricted) 1988-1989 (Box 14)
  - Student Council Goals 1987-1988 (Box 14)
  - Student Health (Restricted) 1987-1989 (Box 14)
  - Student Health 1988-1990 (Box 14)
  - Student Legal Services (Restricted) 1987-1988 (Box 14)
  - Student Legal Services 1988-1990 (Box 14)
  - Student on the Board of Visitors (BOV) (Restricted) 1987-1991 (Box 14)
  - Summer Mailouts 1988-1990 (Box 14)
  - Summer Meetings 1988-1990 (Box 14)
  - Summer Notes 1987-1988 (Box 14)
  - TASC (The Alumni-Student Association) 1987-1990 (Box 15)
  - Tenure (Academics) 1987-1989 (Box 15)
  - Thomas Jefferson Teaching Award and Teaching Awards Committee 1988-1990 (Box 15)
  - Transition Notes 1988-1990 (Box 15)
  - Treasurer's Manual 1987-1988 (Box 15)
  - University Committees 1988-1990 (Box 15)
  - University Journal Contract 1988-1990 (Box 15)
  - University Union 1988-1990 (Box 15)
  - USA Discount Card 1988-1989 (Box 15)
  - Virginia Advocate Defunding 1989 (Box 15)
  - Virginia Student Association (VASA) 1987-1990 (Box 15)
  - VAPSA 1987-1988 (Box 15)
  - Wellness Committee 1988-1990 (Box 15)
  - Women's Concerns (2 Folders) 1987-1990 (Box 15)
  - Year End Report 1988-1990 (Box 15)
- SERIES II: Restricted Files (Box 16)